I don't understand, can you blow the wind?
When I was working on it, you can watch the recording later.
You can control the wind with the wind controller.
In 3D space, right-click in the background, select the simulation attribute, and turn off the gravity.
The gravity is negative 9800.
At this time, all the panels are in the air.
As long as you don't give it external force, it will float.
In this process, you can also use gravity-free.
You can make the panels float or move slowly like this, like in the water.
There is animation.
There is also a kind of pressure that you can give.
About these contents, you can go to the first page.
There are techniques to share about the pressure in the video.
You can see how the pressure works.
You can also see our animation entry.
If you are an animation person, you have to go to the animation entry first.
There is also animation optimization.
If the wind is very hard, please use the internal line and fold a few more internal lines.
For example,
After you finish folding, you may need to go to the outside to make a circle.
How do you go to Baidu to learn how to dress up?
Just go or buy a few books on dressing up.
I actually don't think it's necessary to learn so much about dressing up systematically.
What you have to do is where there is more, where there is less, where there is less.
And you have to add more points to each area to control it.
Clothing sewing line.
Clothing sewing line is made of fake sewing.
Not fake sewing. What fake sewing?
The thread.
Oh my god.
It's too late today.
I made it with thread.
I made it directly with thread.
I pasted it with the thread of the sticker.
You can also use OBJ.
But OBJ thread will add a lot of faces.
I personally don't recommend it.
Just use the existing OBJ.
Or you can use ZB in ZB.
ZB is used for threading.
Or you can also use it in Substance.
You can also use it for threading on the surface.
Now you can also search for version pictures.
If you search for version pictures, you can search on Pinterest.
There will be a variety of English names on Pinterest.
For example,
for example,
is the pattern of shirt.
For GharuZ,
I don't know if it will change because of the right format.
I can't trust Aha.
If you don't use GharuZ,
straight out of the page,
it will change.
Because you can make a triangle with any of the tiles in your MD.
But using Go Z, it seems to be the same two sides.
Because I don't really use ZB, you can try Go Z.
If you don't have any questions, you can follow our Bilibili account and add our QQ group.
Because the number of people in the QQ group is about to reach 3,000.
At the moment, there is no plan to open three groups, so it's not hard.
Thank you for your support.
Don't forget to click on some teaching videos in our homepage.
If you are interested in these teaching videos, you can take a look.
Because there are a lot of content in our live broadcast that we can't talk about too much or we don't have time to talk about it.
You can see a more detailed explanation in those videos.
OK, thank you, thank you, thank you.
Thank you for your support.
That's about it for today's content, okay?
We will...
Oh, right.
I forgot to say something.
This is what I wanted to say last time.
This is the official virtual model of our new Marvelous Designer.
You can download it on our Connect official website.
This is a free model.
There is a girl and a boy.
When do you usually broadcast?
We are looking at the situation.
If there is a live broadcast, it will be notified a few days in advance.
Generally speaking, once a month.
If you are interested, you can download it on our Connect official website.
Or just click on the Marvelous Designer official website.
Then you can find Connect.
This is our official commercial website.
Download this model.
This model is free.
Ah, right.
You can make her a nice dress.
Well, why don't we end today's content here?
See you next time.
Bye bye.
Thank you for your support.
Thank you.
I hope today's video helps you.
See you next time.
Bye bye.
Good night.
See you next time.
Bye bye.